https://ext.vt.edu/about/privacy.html

Skip to Main Content
Home · Jobs · Volunteering · Internships · Giving · Local Offices · News · About
What do you need?
Use the search below to search the site or find your local unit office.
Search...
Agriculture
AgritourismBeef CattleBeginning FarmerCommercial HorticultureCommunity, Local, and Regional Food SystemsCornDairy CattleGraze 300 VAThe Fenceline / Graze 300 VAHempMarket MakerMarket Ready Farm-to-Fork Direct Marketing ResourcesMid-Atlantic Alfalfa Information X-ChangeSheepSilvopasture Silvopastures in Southside Virginia KYForagesSmall GrainsSoil Health and Cover CropsVeterinary MedicineWater, Irrigation, and DrainageIrrigation Workshop 2018Weed ManagementCommunity & Leadership
Leadership & PlanningVALOR ProgramVolunteer with Virginia Cooperative ExtensionFamily
Child Development & ParentingChildren in Home CareDisaster Education NetworkFamily Financial ManagementMaster Financial Education Volunteer ProgramOlder AdultsFood & Health
On-Farm Food SafetyChronic Disease Prevention and Control ProgramsCommunity Food Security and Food SystemsCommunity, Local, and Regional Food SystemsEnology & Fermentation ScienceVirginia Family Nutrition ProgramFood as a BusinessFood Innovations ProgramFood SafetyHome Food PreservationHome Water QualityMaster Food Volunteer ProgramNutrition & WellnessPhysical ActivityServSafe® TrainingLawn & Garden
Annuals, Perennials, and BulbsCommercial HorticultureMaster Gardener ProgramTurf and Garden Tips PodcasttagsbriefsUrban Nutrient ManagementYouth Safety in Lawn CareVegetable GardeningNatural Resources
BiosolidsComposting and Compost UseEnergy Resource Guide for VirginiaForest FarmingForest HarvestingGeospatial Extension ProgramLegacy Planning for Forest LandownersSoil Information ProgramUrban and Community ForestryVirginia Big Tree ProgramVirginia Master Naturalist ProgramWoodland ManagementProducing and marketing natural wood "lump" charcoalCharcoal-making resourcesMarketing resourcesOutreach programs4-H / Youth
4-H All Stars4-H Camping4-H Competitions4-H Foundationscholarships4-H Horse Program4-H Makers4-H Military Partnership4-H Professionals News and Notes4-H SPIN Clubs4-H State Congress4HOnlineCompanion AnimalsHealthy LivingInternational ExchangeNational 4-H CongressNatural Resources and Environmental EducationVirginia 4-H BlogVirginia LifeSmartsYouth Leadership OpportunitiesYouth Livestock ProgramPYD STEM OverviewSTEM in Virginia 4-H 4-H at home
Return to Top
Privacy Statement
Virginia Cooperative Extension has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web page: www.ext.vt.edu and its subdomains.
Information Automatically Logged
The server collects the IP address, date, time, page accessed, browser type, and the referring page if present. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web page. The date and time are used to track the load on the server and peak usage times. We record the browser type to monitor market penetration of various web browsers so we can better determine what Internet technologies we may utilize in the design of our pages. We use page referrer data--that is, information about the web page that pointed you to our page--to determine to what extent our page is referenced by other resources on the web. These data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computing resources.
Personal Information
This site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted without your permission. Personal information that may be requested include your name, e-mail address, physical address, and telephone number.
All forms on this site collect information exclusively for the stated purpose of the form.
We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for purposes other than the reason stated when collected.
Links to Virginia Tech Pages
This site contains links to other Virginia Tech pages. The privacy practices of other pages may vary with the purposes of the page. Consult the privacy statement on each page.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Virginia Tech is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location. User and password information, if requested, is encrypted before it is transmitted across the network.
Users should also consult Virginia Tech's policy on Acceptable Use (PDF).  Virginia Tech complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, contact us.
Follow VCE
Social Media Directory
Need help? Find your city or county's local office.
Publications and Resources
Events and Calendars
Partners
Virginia Tech College of Agriculture and Life Sciences
Virginia State University College of Agriculture
Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station
Virginia Agricultural Research and Extension Centers
Virginia Tech College of Natural Resources and Environment
Contact
Virginia Cooperative Extension programs and employment are open to all, regardless of age, color, disability, gender, gender identity, gender expression, national origin, political affiliation, race, religion, sexual orientation, genetic information, veteran status, or any other basis protected by law. An equal opportunity/affirmative action employer. Issued in furtherance of Cooperative Extension work, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Virginia State University, and the U.S. Department of Agriculture cooperating. Edwin J. Jones, Director, Virginia Cooperative Extension, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, VA 24061, United States; M. Ray McKinnie, Administrator, 1890 Extension Program, Virginia State University, Petersburg, VA, United States.
© 2020 Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
